there's probably something this is
probably something that already exists
with Google Maps but having one giant
map of the city that you get because I
know you can ask your friends to
recommend something and have them add
that you could say okay where the
washrooms where the child activities
will be able to pick all the filters
there's times where maybe you want to
know where the local bathroom is and
then the closest child's facility and
then a coffee shop treat your friend
again this would definitely help with
the errand for any gap but finding like
one map that combines them all that you
get just like the fellowship of course
things that combine everything it would
be and also offers you suggestions as to
which filters you would like on the map
and the more we can put that in we can
put in everything on one map health
rates of cancer the soil sample is one
of the other ones the water quality that
there's an event this Tuesday plan your
time around it there would be a lot of
things we could do with one map that you
can add data to and so that is Apple
number 94 I may have just completely
lost count
bad smart leader